http://www.tomlinsons.com/pages/privacy-policy

Yep, we're open! FREE local deliveries on ALL orders and contactless curbside pickups.
FREE local deliveries on ALL orders and contactless curbside pickups.
Small Animal
What's New?
Small Animal
What's New?
Store Events
On our site we collect the following (only after your consent):
Name
Email address
Mailing address
Phone number
We only collect this information from you when you:
Register on our site
Subscribe to a newsletter
Fill out a form
The information collected from you is used in the following ways:
To improve the website
To improve customer service
To send periodic emails
How do we protect visitor information?
We use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
We use an SSL certificate
We implement security measures when a user: • enters, submits, or accesses their information.
We do not use cookies for tracking purposes
Third Party Disclosure
We may transfer your non-identifiable information to third parties (for example, Google Analytics to track our site traffic). We may also transfer your identifiable information, but only to trusted third parties (for example, the software we use to email you–we will NEVER sell your information to spammers).
Third party links
We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.
Google
We have not enable Google Adwords on our site but we may do so on the future.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
Contact Information:
Tomlinson’s Feed Main Office 910 E. 49 1/2 St. Austin, TX 78751 Telephone: +1 512 452 1560 E-mail: info (at) tomlinsons.com
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes: • On our Privacy Policy Page
Users are able to change their personal information: • By emailing us
How does our site handle do not track signals?
We honor them and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
We do not specifically market to children under 13
Fair Information Practices
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify the users via email
Within 7 business days
We agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors
CAN SPAM Act
We collect your email address:
To send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
To market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to your clients after the original transaction has occured
To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
We will NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
We will identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
We will include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
We will monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
We will honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
We will give an ‘opt-out’ or ‘unsubscribe’ option
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.
Uh oh!
An error occurred while loading the ReCharge checkout!
Please try again.
Copyright © 2020 Tomlinson's Feed.
Powered by Shopify
Web design by Fahrenheit Marketing
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
